(eerie harpsichord music)
("Bad Romance" by Lady Gaga)
♪ Oh-oh-oh-oh-oh, oh-oh-oh-oh, oh-oh-oh ♪
♪ Caught in a bad romance ♪
♪ Rah rah ah-ah-ah ♪
♪ Ro mah ro-mah-mah ♪
Gaga oh-la-la
♪ Want your bad romance ♪
♪ Bah rah ah-ah-ah ♪
♪ Ro mah ro-mah-mah ♪
♪ Gaga ooh-la-la ♪
♪ Want your bad romance ♪
♪ I want your ugly ♪
♪ I want your disease ♪
♪ I want your everything ♪
♪ As long as it's free ♪
♪ I want your love ♪
♪ Love-love-Love, I want your love ♪
♪ Ooh ah ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ want your drama ♪
♪ The touch of your hand, hey ♪
♪ I want your leather
studded kiss in the sand ♪
♪ I want your love ♪
♪ Love-love-love ♪
♪ I want your love,
love-love-love, I want your love ♪
♪ You know that I want you, want you ♪
♪ And you know that I need you ♪
♪ I want it bad, like your bad romance ♪
♪ I want your love and
I want your revenge ♪
♪ You and me could write a bad romance ♪
♪ Oh-oh-oh-oh-oh ♪
♪ I want your love and
all your lover's revenge ♪
♪ You and me could write a bad romance ♪
♪ Oh-oh-oh-oh-oh, oh-oh-oh-oh, oh-oh-oh ♪
♪ Caught in a bad romance ♪
♪ Rah rah ah-ah-ah ♪
♪ Ro mah ro-mah-mah ♪
♪ Gaga ooh-la-la ♪
♪ Want your bad romance ♪
♪ I want your horror, I want your design ♪
♪ 'Cause you're a criminal
as long as your mine ♪
♪ I want your love ♪
♪ Love-love-love, I want your love ♪
♪ Whoa ho ♪
♪ I want your psycho, your
vertigo shtick, shtick, hey ♪
♪ Want you in my rear window ♪
♪ Baby you're sick, I want your love ♪
♪ Love-love-love ♪
♪ I want your love,
love-love-love, I want your love ♪
♪ You know that I want you, want you ♪
♪ And you know that I need you ♪
♪ 'Cause I'm a free bit, baby ♪
♪ I want it bad, like your bad romance ♪
♪ I want your love and
I want your revenge ♪
♪ You and me could write a bad romance ♪
♪ Oh-oh-oh-oh-oh ♪
♪ I want your love and
all your lover's revenge ♪
♪ You and me could write a bad romance ♪
♪ Oh-oh-oh-oh-oh, oh-oh-oh-oh, oh-oh-oh ♪
♪ Caught in a bad romance ♪
♪ Rah rah ah-ah-ah ♪
♪ Ro mah ro-mah-mah ♪
♪ Gaga ooh-la-la ♪
♪ Want your bad romance ♪
♪ Walk, walk, fashion baby ♪
♪ Work it, move that bit crazy ♪
♪ Walk, walk, passion baby ♪
♪ Work it, I'm a free bit baby ♪
♪ I want your love and
I want your revenge ♪
♪ I want your love ♪
♪ I don't wanna be friends ♪
♪ (sings in a foreign language) ♪
♪ I don't wanna be
friends, oh-oh-oh-oh-oh ♪
♪ I want you back ♪
♪ I don't wanna be friends,
caught in a bad romance ♪
♪ I want your bad romance ♪
♪ I don't wanna be
friends, oh-oh-oh-oh-oh ♪
♪ Bad romance, I want you back ♪
♪ Want your bad romance,
caught in a bad romance ♪
♪ Want your bad romance ♪
♪ I want your love and
I want your revenge ♪
♪ You and me could write a bad romance ♪
♪ Oh-oh-oh-oh-oh ♪
♪ I want your love and
all your lover's revenge ♪
♪ You and me could write a bad romance ♪
♪ Oh-oh-oh-oh-oh, oh-oh-oh-oh, oh-oh-oh ♪
♪ Want your bad romance ♪
♪ Caught in a bad romance ♪
♪ Oh-oh-oh-oh-oh, oh-oh-oh-oh, oh-oh-oh ♪
♪ Want your bad romance ♪
♪ Caught in a bad romance ♪
♪ Rah rah ah-ah-ah ♪
♪ Ro mah ro-mah-mah ♪
♪ Gaga ooh-la-la ♪
♪ Want your bad romance ♪
(heavy banging)
(eerie harpsichord music)
(electricity crackling)